BU Records: Retired Professors and Administrators Program, Inclusive: 1947-2020, undated, Bulk:1984-2017
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Biographical and Obituaries, 1947-2020, undated; 3
  - Strain, Lois, 1983-2006 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Streetman, Jean, 1992-2015 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Strickland, C. G., 1979 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Suits, Johnnie Lou, 1999-2011 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Sullivan, Marilyn, 1999-2014 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Summers, Ray, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Sutton, Lois, 2001-2015 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Swain, James, 1991-2001 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Swenson, David, 2017 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Talbert, Charles, 2010-2017 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Tanner, Jr. John, 2015 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Tate, Leone, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Taylor, Joe Maud, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Taylor, Myrtie, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Teaff, Grant G., 2000-2015 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Terry, Christine, 2017 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Thomas, Frances, 1998-2013 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Thomas, Jack W., 1999-2014 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Thomas, Larry J., 2006-2010 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Thomas, Marcelle, 1999-2004 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Thomas, William, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Thompson, E. Bruce, 1999-2003 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Thompson, Tommie R., 2008-2015 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Thomson, Basil H., 2002-2009 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Thornton, Irene, 1989-2013 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Tidmore, F. Eugene, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Tiihonene, Lasse, 2011 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Tindle, Mary, 1998-2018 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Tipton, James, 2009-2014 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Toland, William, 1984-2004 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Tolbert, Sr. Charles M., 1999-2016 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Tolbert, Patricia, 2017 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Toombs, S. Kay, 2001-2012 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Toon, Michael L., 2013-2014 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Townsend, Rosemary, 2015-2016 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Trail, William, 2006-2012 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Treadwell, Louise, 2002-2015 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Trego, Robert “Jim”, 2008-2014 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Trousdale, Valerie, 2015 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Truitt, Cecile, 2004-2014 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Turner, Thomas, 1992-2010 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Tweedie, Virgil, 1998-2007 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Umlauf, Karl, 2015-2018 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Underwood, Kathleen, 1993-2010 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Upton, Nancy, 2007-2014 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Valahu, Dan, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Van Auken, Philip, 2017 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Van Cura, John, 2005-2015 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Vanlandingham, Mary, 2003-2004 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Vardaman, James W., 2000-2018 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Vargas, Robert, 2003-2009 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Vaughn, Adrian, 1998-2005 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Velez, Josephn F., 2001-2018 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Walbesser, Henry H., 2004-2014 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Walker, Lala, 1950-1978 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Walker, Viva, undated (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Walker-Kennedy, Linda, 2011-2014 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Wallace, Patricia, 2009-2017 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Wallace, Susan, 2006-2011 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Wang, Ken-His, 2003-2009 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Ware, W. Browning, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Warren, James, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Wash, Karen, 2016 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Watkins, Julian, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Weatherford, Dewayne, 1999-2018 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Weaver, Patricia, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Wellbaum, Kay, 1991-2011 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Wells, Ruby, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Wendorf, Mary, 1992-2011 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - West, David, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Westerfield, Butler, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - White, Bon-Jean, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - White, Edna, 1998-2017 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - White, Ellen, 2017 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - White, William, 1948-1963 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Whitley, Glenna, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Wicker, Christine, undated (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Widner, Dorothy, 1992-2008 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Wienandt, Pat, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Wiese, Walter Clifford Jr., undated (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Wiley, James W., 2004-2011 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Willbanks, Eulalie T., undated (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Williams, J. Clifton, 1998-2012 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Williams, James, 2014-2015 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Williams, Jane, 2005-2009 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Williams, Margie, 1999-2012 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Williams, Sidney, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Williams, Stephen L., 2007-2014 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Williams, Walter & Lucy Sue, 1972-1977 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Williams, W. C., 1992-2018 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Williams-Lummus, undated (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Williamson, James, 2003-2014 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Willis, Carolyn B., 1998-2012 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Wilson, Dorothy, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Wilson, Gordon, 2006-2009 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Wilson, John, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Wimer, Jack W., 1999-2017 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Wimpee, W. J, 1990-2005 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Wise, Elizabeth S., 2000-2013 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Witte, Mary, 2017 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Wolf, Barbara, 2009-2011 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Wood, James Jr., 1974-2004 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Wood, John A., 2004-2014 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Woods, Paula, 2007-2009 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Wortman, Walter, 1999-2018 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Wosnitza, Regine, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Wright, Scott, undated (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Yantis, Mary Ann, 2009 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Yates, Kyle M., 1975 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Young, David, 2012 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Young, Robert H., 1998-2017 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Deceased Members from Old Newsletters, 1980-1991 (Box 26, Folder 30)